Lying on the sofa, sternal precautions moving
slow. The fire in my mind is starting to ignite
and grow. I'm not a patient, not a victim. I'm a
student, I'm a man. And I am not just healing. I am
making a new plan. English 102, a final grade.
The eight of us, a single team. We're not just
going to pass this class. We're going to build a
dream.
The accessibility project, it's not about the
money. It's not about the ramps we need. It's the
failure of the map. The information's all a
trap. We'll write the code, we'll fix the line.
And give them all the proper signs. This is our
new proposal. This is our counterattack.
I know the paths, I know the pain, the broken
lists, the pouring rain, the elevator no one
knows, the hidden route that never shows, on
their own, broken P.D.S. It's time we show them
what is love
English 102, a final grade The eight of us, a
single team We're not just gonna pass this class
We're gonna build a dream
The accessibility project, it's not about the
money. It's not about the ramps we need. It's the
failure of the map. The information's all a
trap. We'll write the code, we'll fence the
lines And give them all the proper signs This is
our new proposal This is our counter-attack
I'm still healing, I'm not strong But I will
stand before that room Daniel will drive me, I
will be there And I will break this awful gloom I
will use my voice, I will make the choice
The
accessibility project, it's not about the
money. It's not about the ramps we need. It's the
failure of the map. The information's all a
trap. We'll write the code, we'll fix the lines,
and give them all the proper signs. This is our
new proposal. This is our counterattack.
We're not just getting an A. We're starting a
revolution.